Guide to the University Christian Movement Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Program Records, Series II
  - Field Service Committee
    - Administrative records
      - Southwest Georgia Project, Student Interracial Ministry, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 148)
      - Statement by Reverend Henry Bucher Jr re. the turning in of his draft card, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 149)
      - UCM committee lists, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 150)
      - UCM policy and strategy documents, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - Field Staff
      - Anderson, Steve. Student activist in Ohio. Assisted with Process '67 program planning, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 152)
      - Bunch, Charlotte. Promoted UCM in Washington, D.C. Includes Bunch's "Speech for Jeanette Rankin Brigade--Women's Congress on U.S. foreign policy", 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 153)
      - Durrett, Phil. Worked with the Free University of Illinois and organized students in Champagne-Urbana area., 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 154)
      - Faggetter, Rachel. International Travel Associate from Australia. Traveled through the midwest and west coast promoting UCM and Process '67 conference on college campuses., 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 155)
      - Goff, Fred. Worked closely with North American Congress on Latin America (NACLA). Includes report "The Violence of Domination: U.S. Power and the Dominican Republic" by Fred Goff and Michael Locker, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 156)
      - Gunn, Bob. Organized Depth Education Groups in coordination with Process '67 conference in the New York City are., 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 157)
      - Hedleston, Jo Ann. Worked closely with Students for a Democratic Society in Columbia, Missouri., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 158)
      - Hedlund, Sonja. Intern at the United Nations., 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 159)
      - Hedlun, Sonja, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 160)
      - Huang, Hsing Peng. International Travel Associate from Singapore, and traveled through the mid west and southeast promoting UCM on college campuses., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 161)
      - Huang, Hsing Peng, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 162)
      - Huang, Hsing Peng, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 163)
      - Jenkins, Jo and Maureen. Based in Seattle, Washington. Includes Students for a Democratic Society report "Wind in the Fields: a Report on Farm Labors, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 164)
      - Johnson, Steve. Located in Ann Arbor, Michigan, and worked with the Radical Education Project initiated by the Students for a Democratic Society. Includes REP Newsletter and program description., 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 165)
      - Kean, Rick and Miller, Patti. Miller was a campus organizer who had worked with Southern Christian Leadership Conference in Chicago in the "Project to End Slums." Kean attempted to build a communication network in the midwest., 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 166)
      - Kendricks, Elmira. Intern at the United Nations., 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 167)
      - Kittredge, Jack. Located in Chicago, Illinois, Kittredge traveled through the midwest promoting NSCF/UCM and SDS. Includes [SDS] Chapter Organizer's Handbook by Jack Kittredge, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 168)
      - Kittredge, Jack and Reames, Phyl, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 169)
      - Liljenstolpe, Otto. Co-sponsored by UCM and the Fellowship of Reconciliation in Chicago to be an organizer focused on peace education., 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 170)
      - Lobenstine, Clark. In charge of the Political Concerns Commission of the UCM., 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 171)
      - McCurdy, Sheila. Organized law students at Rutgers University to represent welfare recipients., 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 172)
      - Miller, Patti. Campus organizer who had worked with Southern Christian Leadership Conference in Chicago in the "Project to End Slums.". Includes flyers, news clippings, stickers., 1966 (Box 12, Folder 173)
      - Miller, Patti. Includes photograph of Miller and news clippings., 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 174)
      - Romberg, Jim. Southwest Georgia Project, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 175)
      - Rominski, Fran. An organizer from the Young Christian Students group in San Francisco Bay Area., 1966 (Box 12, Folder 176)
      - Spencer, Howard. Worked with civil rights activists in Mississippi. Includes untitled newsletter with report on Stokely Carmichael's visit to Tougaloo College, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 177)
      - Talbot, Richard. Student activist in St. Could, Minnesota., 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 178)
  - Political Concerns Committee
    - Conference on International Conflict and Violence, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - Contacts, 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 180)
    - Correspondence, General, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 181)
    - Correspondence, Threadgill, Rix, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - Correspondence and notes of Clark Lobenstine re. proposed UCM-Puerto Rico project, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 183)
    - Correspondence re. UCM's minimal political stance, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 184)
    - Correspondence, United States National Student Association, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - Correspondence re. migrant workers, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 186)
    - Meeting minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 187)
    - Meeting minutes and notes of Clark Lobenstine, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 188)
    - Memos, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 189)
    - Originals for ecnolith. Materials re. the draft., undated (Box 13, Folder 190)
    - Paper: "Political Attitudes of Students in the U.S." by Jill Hultin, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 191)
    - Pax Romana bulletin, undated (Box 13, Folder 192)
    - Reports and working papers, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 193)
    - Task forces and UCM's political relevance, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 194)
    - Topical: Education, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 195)
    - Topical: Latin America, 1965-1968 (Box 13, Folder 196)
    - Topical: The unseating of Representative Adam Clayton Powell from chairmanship of the House Education and Labor Committee., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 197)
    - Topical: Vietnam and the draft, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 198)
    - Topical: Vietnam War, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 199)
    - Topical: Vietnam draft, Black Power movement, and academic freedom, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 200)
    - Working file of Allan Burry, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 201)
  - Caucuses and Task Forces
    - Black Caucus, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 209)
    - Ideology Task Force, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 210)
    - International Caucus, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 211)
    - Latin American Concerns Task Force: Consolation on Latin America Concerns, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 212)
    - Latin American Concerns Task Force: Contact lists, meeting minutes, and reports, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 213)
    - Latin American Concerns Task Force: Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 214)
    - Latin American Concerns Task Force: Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 215)
    - Latin American Concerns Task Force: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 216)
    - Latin American Concerns Task Force: Puerto Rico study project, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 217)
    - Middle East Task Force, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 218)
    - Phillipines-U.S. Task Force, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 219)
    - Radical Caucus, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 220)
    - Southern Africa Committee: Correspondence mostly carbon copies of letters from UCM of South Africa, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 221)
    - Southern Africa Committee: Letters from unknown student who was traveling in South Africa, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 222)
    - Southern Africa Committee: Meeting minutes, publications, and reports, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 223)
    - UCM-United Ministries in Higher Education Task Force on Internationalization of Higher Education: Carbon copy letters of Poikal George, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 224)
    - UCM-UMHE Internationalization Task Force: Correspondence of Paul Schrading, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 225)
    - UCM-UMHE Internationalization Task Force: Consultation on Internationalization in Higher Education and the Church's ministry, 1967 November 8-10 (Box 16, Folder 226)
    - UCM-UMHE Internationalization Task Force: Meeting minutes and reports, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 227)
    - UCM-UMHE Internationalization Task Force: Memos, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 228)
    - UCM-UMHE Internationalization Task Force: Participants in overseas orientation programs, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 229)
    - UCM-UMHE Internationalization Task Force: UCM summer seminar on Asia, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 230)
  - Committee on International Ecumenical Ministry
    - Brochures and Asia bibliography, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 231)
    - Correspondence and inter-office communication, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 232)
    - Correspondence re. The Bridge ministry, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 233)
    - International Christian ministry at Berkeley, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 234)
    - Meeting minutes and memos, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 235)
    - Papers and reports, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 236)
    - Proposals, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 237)
  - Committee on Study Resources and Publications
    - Articles and news clippings re. UCM, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 238)
    - Correspondence, General, 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 239)
    - Correspondence, General assembly includes news release, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 240)
    - Correspondence, Sund, Tecla, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 241)
    - Correspondence of Leon Howell (Publication Secretary), 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 242)
    - Correspondence re. Dialogue books, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 243)
    - Correspondence re. orders for Communique, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 244)
    - Committee on Communication: Meeting minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 245)
    - Communication Consultation, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 246)
    - Department of Publication Services of the National Council of Churches: Publication reports, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 247)
    - Drafts of Second Look newsletter, undated (Box 17, Folder 248)
    - Meeting minutes, 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 249)
    - Memos re. publication inventory, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 250)
    - Provactive resources for group study, discussions, and worship, undated (Box 18, Folder 251)
    - Publications re. Higher Education, Internationalization, and Vietnam War, undated (Box 18, Folder 252)
    - Scrapbook re. UCM creation. Contains news clippings and news releases. Removed from binder due to preservation concerns., 1966 (Box 23, Folder 314)
    - UCM background and articles, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 253)
  - Theological Reflection Committee
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 254)
    - Meeting minutes, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 255)
    - Memos includes progress report, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 256)
    - "Our Story: Some Further Reflections of Operation of UCM" Includes correspondence and drafts, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 257)
    - Research materials including The Christian Community in the Academic World: a Statement approved by the General Committee of the World Student Christian Federation, 1964, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 258)
- Publications, Series III
  - Booklet: Education and Social Change: Notes from the UCM Files, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 259)
  - Brochures, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 260)
  - Miscellaneous printed material distributed by UCM, 1967, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 261)
  - Miscellaneous printed material distributed by UCM, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 262)
  - Miscellaneous printed material distributed by UCM, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 263)
  - Miscellaneous printed material distributed by UCM, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 264)
  - The Second Look: Analyzing World Issues of Interests to Students (newsletter), 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 265)
  - The Second Look: Analyzing World Issues of Interests to Students (newsletter), 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 266)
  - The Second Look: Analyzing World Issues of Interests to Students (newsletter), 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 267)
  - Wind and Chaff: a Student Journal of the University Christian Movement, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 268)
- Conferences, Series IV
  - Annual Assembly
    - UCM Annual Assembly I, McCormick Theological Seminary, Chicago, IL, 1966 September 4-9
      - Annual assembly file of M.O. Williams (Box 20, Folder 269)
      - Articles, news clippings re. formation of UCM (Box 20, Folder 270)
      - Articles of Operation of the UCM in the USA (Box 20, Folder 271)
      - Articles of Operation of the UCM in the USA including notes of M.O. Williams (Box 20, Folder 272)
      - Correspondence of Paul Schrading (Associate General Secretary) (Box 20, Folder 273)
      - Meeting materials and notes of M.O. Williams (Box 20, Folder 274)
      - Meeting minutes of the assembly (Box 20, Folder 275)
      - Memos and meeting minutes (Box 20, Folder 276)
      - Nominations (Box 20, Folder 277)
      - Notes of Paul Schrading (Associate General Secretary) (Box 20, Folder 278)
      - Proposed sequence of events for the annual assembly, registration forms, and rules of order (Box 20, Folder 279)
      - Reports to the assembly and resolutions (Box 20, Folder 280)
      - Roster of attendees (Box 20, Folder 281)
    - UCM Annual Assembly II, Loyola University, Chicago, IL, 1967 June 11-16
      - Correspondence re. location of conference (Box 21, Folder 282)
      - Correspondence re. past due accounts (Box 21, Folder 283)
      - Correspondence re. program planning and request for financial assistance (Box 21, Folder 284)
      - Liturgy (Box 21, Folder 285)
      - Meeting minutes of the assembly (Box 21, Folder 286)
      - Memos, reports, and statements (Box 21, Folder 287)
      - Mini minutes of post Annual Assembly General Committee and reports (Box 21, Folder 288)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 289)
      - Notes on program for annual assembly (Box 21, Folder 290)
      - Program planning (Box 21, Folder 291)
      - Registration materials including transcript of notations written on the backs of registration blanks (Box 21, Folder 292)
      - Resolutions (Box 21, Folder 293)
    - UCM Annual Assembly III, Webster College, St. Louis, MO, June 10-15, 1968
      - Conference materials (Box 21, Folder 294)
      - Correspondence re. location of conference (Box 21, Folder 295)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 296)
      - Correspondence re. program planning. Includes notes of Paul Schrading (Box 21, Folder 297)
      - Credentials Committee notebook and ballots for UCM officers (Box 22, Folder 298)
      - Drafts of meeting minutes (Box 22, Folder 299)
      - Drafts of reports (Box 22, Folder 300)
      - "Impressions of the University Christian Movement General Assembly" by H.D. Bollinger (Box 22, Folder 301)
      - Meeting minutes of the assembly (Box 22, Folder 302)
      - Membership committee (Box 22, Folder 303)
      - News clippings from T he Texas Methodist: Weekly Newspaper of the Methodist Church re. annual assembly (Box 22, Folder 304)
      - Nominations and job descriptions (Box 22, Folder 305)
      - "Our Story" working paper and response (Box 22, Folder 306)
      - "Reflections on Our Second Year" progress report (Box 22, Folder 307)
      - Registration form and promotion materials (Box 22, Folder 308)
      - Reports (Box 22, Folder 309)
      - Reports from Issue Workshops (Box 22, Folder 310)
      - Special invitations (Box 22, Folder 311)
  - Process '67, Cleveland, OH, 1967 December 26-1968 January 1
    - Advisory Committee: Correspondence and meeting minutes, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 312)
    - Advisory Committee: Correspondence including nominations to the committee, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 313)
    - "Additional Comments and Questions to be Pondered prior to Cleveland", 1967 (Box 24, Folder 315)
    - Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 316)
    - Cleveland week roster of attendees, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 317)
    - Committee on Internationalization: Memos and minutes, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 318)
    - Conference materials and conference coordinating materials of Paul Schrading, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 319)
    - Correspondence re. Planning Committee, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 320)
    - Correspondence, Brandenburg, Art, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 321)
    - Correspondence, Committee on Internationalization with student Christian movements from other countries, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 322)
    - Correspondence, Danforth Foundation, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 323)
    - Correspondence, Sheraton Hotel, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 324)
    - Correspondence re. arts at the conference, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 325)
    - Correspondence re. Canadian student Christian movement delegates, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 326)
    - Correspondence, Committee on Internationalization, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 327)
    - Correspondence, Committee on Internationalization with student Christian movements from other countries, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 328)
    - Correspondence re. conference planning. Includes statement on the Vietnam War draft and "Who Formulates Public Opinion: a Depth Education Group Study", 1967 (Box 24, Folder 329)
    - Correspondence re. Depth Education Groups, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 330)
    - Correspondence re. Depth Education Groups, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 331)
    - Correspondence re. Depth Education Group resource leaders and people, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 332)
    - Correspondence re. Depth Education Group resource leaders and people, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 333)
    - Correspondence re. dialogue focusers for Depth Education Groups and requests for scholarship funding, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 334)
    - Correspondence re. Ecumenical exchange scholarship, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 335)
    - Correspondence re. Fall travel of Huang Hsing Peng and Rachel Faggetter. Includes reports., 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 336)
    - Correspondence re. films shown at Process '67, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 337)
    - Correspondence re. finances, mostly with conference hotel, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 338)
    - Correspondence re. financial contributions, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 339)
    - Correspondence re. funding and programming, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 340)
    - Correspondence re. fund raising and program coordination, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 341)
    - Correspondence re. ham radio network set up at Process '67, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 342)
    - Correspondence re. internationalization of television program at Process '67, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 343)
    - Correspondence, Jones, Karen including progress reports from Cleveland field staff, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 344)
    - Correspondence re. local arrangements, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 345)
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 346)
    - Correspondence re. requests for funding, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 347)
    - Correspondence re. resource leaders, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 348)
    - Correspondence re. scholarships, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 349)
    - Correspondence, Simmons, Donald J., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 350)
    - Correspondence re. transportation, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 351)
    - Correspondence, Van Voorhis, Richard, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 352)
    - Depth Education Group coordinating materials, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 353)
    - Depth Education Group evaluations by leaders. Includes papers, notes, and report from Aid, Trade and Development, Course of U.S. Policy in Southeast Asia, Student Power, Curriculum Reform, and Alternative Model for the University DEGs., 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 354)
    - Depth Education Group evaluations by leaders. Includes papers and reports from Black Power, Legal and Moral Rights of the Poor, and Poverty DEGS., 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 355)
    - Depth Education Group evaluations by leaders. Includes papers and reports from Mass Media, Public Opinion, Politics, White Power, and Exploitation of the Ghetto DEGs, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 356)
    - Depth Education Group evaluations by participants, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 357)
    - Depth Education Group Memos and materials, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 358)
    - Depth Education Group program planning and materials for leaders, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 359)
    - Depth Education Group, Report on UCM trip for Depth Education workshops made by John McCabe and Karen Jones, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 360)
    - Depth Education Group reply forms from DEG leaders and coordinators, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 361)
    - Depth Education Group reply forms from DEG leaders and coordinators, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 362)
    - Depth Education Group reports, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 363)
    - Depth Education Groups reports and reviews, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 364)
    - Depth Education Groups, research materials, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 365)
    - Dialogue Focus paper on education by Richard Kean, undated (Box 27, Folder 366)
    - Evaluation, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 367)
    - Everything that Could Have Happened and This is the Report (Official UCM report on Process '67. Includes draft), 1968 (Box 28, Folder 368)
    - Executive Committee correspondence, meeting minutes, and information about Nebraska Free University, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 369)
    - Executive Committee meeting minutes and reports, 1965-1967 (Box 28, Folder 370)
    - Executive Committee memos and meeting min, 1965-1967 (Box 28, Folder 371)
    - Executive Committee memos, meeting minutes, and reports, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 372)
    - Executive Committee meeting minutes and reports, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 373)
    - Executive Committee memos and minutes, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 374)
    - Executive Committee reports, 1965-1967 (Box 29, Folder 375)
    - File of Clark Lobenstine. Includes memos, promotional materials, and DEG information., 1967 (Box 29, Folder 376)
    - Follow up mailing to anyone who signed up for UCM materials. Includes DEG reports and articles., 1968 (Box 29, Folder 377)
    - Input resources including various papers, film list, issues of Commonweal, "The Student's Role in College Policy-Making", 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 378)
    - Input resources including papers on Vietnam War/Draft and Sexual Revolution, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 379)
    - Look Up and Live materials and news clippings, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 380)
    - Mailing regarding Depth Education Groups, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 381)
    - Meeting minutes, memos, and notes of M.O. Williams, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 382)
    - News clippings from The Cleveland Plain Dealer and The Cleveland Press covering Process '67, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 383)
    - Planning Committee, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 384)
    - The Preceptor cards (Closed circuit tv show at Process '67), news for immediate release, reports, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 385)
    - Pre-conference packet, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 386)
    - Promotion in Canada, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 387)
    - Promotion mailings to DHL-MML, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 388)
    - Promotion materials, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 389)
    - Project: "Choice" a Community Education--Communication Project 1967-68 Broadcast Season Sponsored by the Department of Radio and Television Metropolitan Detroit Council of Churches (Box 30, Folder 390)
    - Proposal for "The Facilitator" project which was an interview and computer matching program to pair people with like interests, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 391)
    - Report of Charlotte Bunch re. Process '67, working notes of to do lists, and memos around the UCM office, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 392)
    - Report of the Claremont delegation, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 393)
    - Report to UCM General Committee re. Depth Education Groups, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 394)
    - Resource people for Depth Education Groups, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 395)
    - Resource pool forms, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 396)
    - Reviews of Process '67, articles, letters, and reports, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 397)
    - Reviews of Process '67, articles, letters, and reports, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 398)
    - Scrapbook (removed from binder due to preservation concerns), 1968 (Box 31, Folder 399)
    - Scrapbook (removed from binder due to preservation concerns), 1968 (Box 31, Folder 400)
    - Scrapbook (removed from binder due to preservation concerns), 1968 (Box 31, Folder 401)
    - Working party on Internationalization, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 402)
  - Other Conferences, Consultations, and Seminars